<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zeya Xue</title>
    <link>https://zeyaxue.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zeya Xue</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zeyaxue.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rekindled love for an old hobby - hand embroidery</title>
      <link>https://zeyaxue.github.io/post/rekindled-love-for-an-old-hobby-hand-embroidery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeyaxue.github.io/post/rekindled-love-for-an-old-hobby-hand-embroidery/</guid>
      <description>Deja vu about a 10-year-old me I was taught how to embroider by my grandma back when I was 10 years old. It was summer time with no school but the weather is unbearaly hot with high humidity. I did not feel like going outside and play with other kids in the heat. Then, I saw my grandma sewing something and I became interested and probably baggered her to let me play with needles and threads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD commencement </title>
      <link>https://zeyaxue.github.io/post/phd-commencement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeyaxue.github.io/post/phd-commencement/</guid>
      <description>On June 13, I had my PhD commencement. However, the ceremony itself is not an end to my PhD life, I was still &amp;ldquo;neck-deep&amp;rdquo; in writing/modifying dissertation for the past month or so. I have sent my dissertation draft to my committee members and now I can finally catch a breath and make a post.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a professional shot picture (i.e. $20 per photo) of my PI, Maria Marco and I.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post speeding up science hackathon</title>
      <link>https://zeyaxue.github.io/post/post-speeding-up-science-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeyaxue.github.io/post/post-speeding-up-science-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>What is the speeding up science workshop/hackathon? Direct quote from the organizer Holly Bik and Titus Brown: Speeding up Science&amp;quot; is a series of workshops focused on developing application-specific Jupyter notebooks which are executable/launchable via Binder. The goal of these workshops is to “reverse engineer” common data visualization approaches used for biological data analysis and commonly published in scientific journal articles (heatmaps, read/OTU summaries, etc.).
Here’s a link to the workshop GitHub and all the visualization workflows came from the workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>https://zeyaxue.github.io/post/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeyaxue.github.io/post/first-post/</guid>
      <description> Hello world! This is the 1st post as a test for using Blogdown to make a website with Huabing’s clean white theme for Hugo.
Acutal life note: I came back from dinner at Wen and Nada’s place. As usual, they are uber nice and I’m amazed by how agile Wen is at the age of 95. Wish him good health for many years to come!!!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zeyaxue.github.io/search/placeholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeyaxue.github.io/search/placeholder/</guid>
      <description> This page is still under construction. New feature coming soon! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://zeyaxue.github.io/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeyaxue.github.io/top/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Zhengyao (Zeya) Xue. 中文名是薛正遥。I am currently a PhD candidate at University of California Davis. I got my BS from Nanjing University, China. You can find more about more work at the publications page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://zeyaxue.github.io/top/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zeyaxue.github.io/top/publications/</guid>
      <description>Google Scholar Profile
2019  Kable, Mary E., Yanin Srisengfa, Zhengyao Xue, Laurynne C. Coates, and Maria L. Marco. &amp;ldquo;Viable and total bacterial populations undergo equipment-and time-dependent shifts during milk processing.&amp;rdquo; Appl. Environ. Microbiol. (2019): AEM-00270.DOI: 10.1128/AEM.00270-19
 Appelt, Sandra, Sharif S. Aly, Karen Tonooka, Kathy Glenn, Zhengyao Xue, Terry W. Lehenbauer, and Maria L. Marco. Development and comparison of loop-mediated isothermal amplification and quantitative polymerase chain reaction assays for the detection of Mycoplasma bovis in milk.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>